let savollar15 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "affair",
        answer: "C. ish",
        options: [
            "A. bayram",
            "B. sir",
            "C. ish",
            "D. do'stlik"
        ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "assembly",
      answer: "A. yig'ilish",
      options: [
        "A. yig'ilish",
        "B. ma'ruza",
        "C. jamoa",
        "D. sinf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to bless",
      answer: "B. duo qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. so'ramoq",
        "B. duo qilmoq",
        "C. himoya qilmoq",
        "D. eshitmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "cereal",
    answer: "B. donli mahsulot",
    options: [
        "A. non",
        "B. donli mahsulot",
        "C. sharbat",
        "D. qahva"
    ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "cheerful",
      answer: "A. quvnoq",
      options: [
        "A. quvnoq",
        "B. jahldor",
        "C. xafa",
        "D. charchagan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "diameter",
      answer: "C. diametr",
      options: [
        "A. perimetr",
        "B. maydon",
        "C. diametr",
        "D. hajm"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "to exploit",
      answer: "D. suiiste'mol qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yordam bermoq",
        "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
        "C. targ'ib qilmoq",
        "D. suiiste'mol qilmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "famine",
      answer: "B. ocharchilik",
      options: [
        "A. boylik",
        "B. ocharchilik",
        "C. qurg'oqchilik",
        "D. suvsizlik"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "harvest",
        answer: "D. hosil",
        options: [
            "A. ekish",
            "B. haydash",
            "C. sug'orish",
            "D. hosil"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "merry",
        answer: "A. xursand",
        options: [
            "A. xursand",
            "B. jiddiy",
            "C. tinch",
            "D. sokin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "nut",
        answer: "B. yong'oq",
        options: [
            "A. urug'",
            "B. yong'oq",
            "C. po'choq",
            "D. po'st"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "to pardon",
        answer: "D. kechirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. so'ramoq",
            "B. qaytarmoq",
            "C. eshitmoq",
            "D. kechirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "pharaoh",
      answer: "C. fir'avn",
      options: [
          "A. shoh",
          "B. prezident",
          "C. fir'avn",
          "D. hukmdor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "ripe",
        answer: "A. yetilgan",
        options: [
            "A. yetilgan",
            "B. xom",
            "C. yangi",
            "D. eski"
        ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to roast",
      answer: "A. qovurmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qovurmoq",
        "B. pishirmoq",
        "C. bug'da pishirmoq",
        "D. qaynatmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "routine",
      answer: "B. odatiy tartib",
      options: [
        "A. tartibsizlik",
        "B. odatiy tartib",
        "C. tasodif",
        "D. reja"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "scheme",
      answer: "C. reja",
      options: [
        "A. tartibsizlik",
        "B. ro'yxat",
        "C. reja",
        "D. naqsh"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "slim",
      answer: "D. ozg'in",
      options: [
        "A. semiz",
        "B. keng",
        "C. yupqa",
        "D. ozg'in"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "stove",
      answer: "B. plita",
      options: [
        "A. muzlatkich",
        "B. plita",
        "C. rakovina",
        "D. pech"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "theft",
      answer: "A. o'g'irlik",
      options: [
        "A. o'g'irlik",
        "B. talonchilik",
        "C. odam o'g'irlash",
        "D. buzib kirish"
      ]
    }
  ];
  export default savollar15;
  